♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey.
What are you working on?
Oh, just trying to make some
sense of these numbers.
What the...
What did you hit?
What happened to
my spreadsheet?
What exactly was the endgame
if I hadn't walked in?
Ugh, there's nothing worse
than grocery shopping
on the day before
Thanksgiving.
Yeah, that's the sound
a rich family's turkey makes.
There's still a lot more
groceries in the car.
Well, it's not a race.
Take a break.
Ugh, if you knew
how close we were
to putting you
down last year.
Geez, what's her problem?
Eh, Thanksgiving's
exhausting.
You know what
she could use?
A little sip
of that drink I invented.
Hi! Stewie Griffin here
with my latest creation:
Monster Energy Drink.
What is it? I don't know,
but it's free from this truck
that stopped outside your work.
Mix it with booze. Ever been
wide-awake-blacked-out?
Ever try to jump over
a train on a bike?
Ever bit the beak off a bird?
Monster Energy:
put it in your body
and ask questions later.
It's green, so it's nature.
We now return to Guy Friends.
So, you must
be pretty pumped.
For what?
Oh. Olympics.
Oh, yeah. I guess
that's starting soon.
I thought you were
a big Olympics guy.
Yeah, I like 'em okay.
Huh.
♪ Guy friends ♪
♪ A computer made us
roommates in college ♪
♪ That's why we're friends ♪
♪ Guy friends! ♪
Mail's here.
Any fliers of Hispanic women
running for city council?
Yeah, there is.
Thank you.
Peter, you got a letter
from your sister Karen.
What? You've got
a sister, Dad?
How come we've
never met her?
Is she a prim and proper
aunt
or a big, fat,
dirty aunt?
I have no obligation
to tell any of you anything.
Mr. Griffin has shown good
faith in appearing here today
and will not be subjected
to this sort of
hostile interrogation.
Your father doesn't like to
talk about his sister, Meg.
They've never
really gotten along.
Wow, Peter.
In all the years I've known you,
you've never even
mentioned a sister.
Big deal, I don't
talk about my sister.
I also don't talk about
that tickling uncle.
All right, Uncle Dan,
remember: no tickling.
You got it.
You didn't say anything
about Uncle Neil.
Whose uncles are you?
It says here your sister's
coming for Thanksgiving.
She what?
If we're having
guests, can I invite
Rosario Vargas from
the third district,
a leader you
can depend on?
I don't want
Karen here.
Peter, you've been avoiding
your sister for too long.
Besides, she says she's been
having Thanksgiving
with your mother for
the last 20 years.
And now that your mom
has passed,
she'd like to spend
Thanksgiving with you.
No.
Peter, Karen's coming
and that's that.
How cool! I didn't
even know I had an aunt.
I can't wait
to meet her.
Look, I'm telling you guys,
it's gonna be a disaster.
Just like the alternate
ending of Back to the Future.
♪ ♪
Well, if I'm gonna
disappear into nothing,
I might as well bang my mom.
Hey, Lorraine, wait up!
Hi! My name's Marty!
I'm in a picture!
♪ ♪
To be contondered!
We now return to The Cosby Show,
knowing what we know now.
Huh. I was so busy
not seeing color,
I didn't see the raping, either.
Okay, everyone.
It'll be another hour
before the turkey's done,
but I made more appetizers.
Ooh, grape jelly on a Triscuit.
You're a whiz.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down.
Save your appetite.
And don't think
I haven't noticed
you've already had two drinks.
You're, like, all the worst
parts of a girlfriend.
Oh. That must be Karen.
I'll get it. Aunt Karen?
And you must be Meg.
Do that to me!
Wow, it's so cool that I've got
an aunt I didn't know about.
Oh, Karen, I'm so happy
you could make it.
Lois Pewterschmidt.
The one that got away.
I'm just joshing, kid.
Auntie's not a biscuit-bumper.
I'm not, either!
Peter, come say hello
to your sister.
Fine.
Hey, Karen.
Welcome to our...
Bring it in, Pee Pee!
I like her.
Hello. I am City Councilwoman
Rosario Vargas.
Quahog doesn't work if
it doesn't work for all of us.
That's a beautiful
pantsuit, Ms. Vargas.
Wow, Karen,
nice to meet you.
I'm Glenn Quagmire.
I didn't know
Peter even had a sister.
What are you,
ashamed of me, Chin Nuts?
Oh, my God. His chin kind
of does look like nuts.
Ha, ha! I never
noticed that.
How could you
not notice it?
Watch this,
I-I'll punch him in the nuts.
Eh, sort of clever.
Wait a second. I know you.
You're that lady wrestler.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
he's right.
Hey, w-what do they
call you again?
Heavy Flo.
You're Heavy Flo!
In the flesh and blood.
Gross.
Man, you're amazing.
I remember when you called out
Andrea the Giant
the day after September 11.
What just happened was
a national tragedy,
but it's nothing compared
to what I'm gonna do
to Andrea the Giant!
We will never forget
what happened yesterday,
but you'll also never forget
what's gonna happen September 17
at the Jack Witschi
Sports Arena!
Peter, I can't believe you've
kept your sister a secret.
She's amazing!
Yeah, she's crazy strong.
Like Superman on a date.
Yeah, I wasn't here,
but I heard her scream,
so I came flying in
and found her like this.
It's weird.
Same cause of death
as those three guys
in that local public bathroom.
Unsolvable.
Now do you see why I didn't
want Karen here, Lois?
She terrorized me
my whole childhood.
Now she's got to embarrass
me in front of my friends?
Peter, Bonnie just
changed Joe on the table.
What are you
worried about?
Still, I don't want
to go back out there.
Look, I know
you've had your differences,
but Karen's your sister.
And you're grown-ups now.
Can't you just go out there
and pretend to have a good time?
Fine, I'll play along.
I guess I've lied before.
Where you going?
Home.
Where's home?
The White House.
Okay, I'm here.
This is my house.
You can go now.
Thanks for taking me home.
Go ahead, go inside.
I will.
You can drive away now.
No, no, I-I want to make
sure you get inside safe.
Yeah, but I-I got to look
through the mail first.
You know how it is.
Really, I insist.
I-It's totally okay. Go.
At this point, it's more
about me than it is you.
It's a bad
neighborhood.
If I don't see
you go inside,
I'll be thinking
about it all night.
Uh... come on in,
Mr. President!
And then, so I'm like, "Peter,
how was I supposed to know
you didn't want your teammates
to know you wore a bra?"
It was a custom-designed
sports halter top.
More stories!
Hey, tell one where
Peter is a nincompoop
or maybe a Silly Billy.
Oh, man.
Okay, let's just
carve the turkey.
Oh, Aunt Karen
already carved it.
She did?
But that's my thing.
I always do my "are you a leg
man or a breast man" joke.
Aunt Karen
did that, too.
It was hilarious.
I never really got it
until she said it.
Ha, ha!
Hey, Karen,
later you got to show us
some of your wrestling holds.
Yeah, what's that trademark
finishing move of yours?
The Toxic Shock.
Oh, yeah,
that move is badass!
You're awesome.
Know what else is awesome?
This stuffing.
Thank you, Glenn.
You're welcome.
I'm in a good mood.
Sure, what the hell,
I'll show you my moves.
Maybe after dinner.
No, no, no. The family
football game is after dinner.
We do it every year!
Peter, calm down.
You're making a scene.
It's not my fault, Lois.
She's ruining Thanksgiving!
The way Tim Burton
ruined the Fourth of July!
♪ Spooky! Happy!
Spooky! Happy! ♪
♪ Weirdness! Weirdness! ♪
♪ Spooky! Happy! ♪
♪ La, la, la! ♪
♪ Weirdness, weirdness ♪
♪ Patriotic weirdness ♪
♪ Barbecuing human heads ♪
♪ Every president is dead ♪
♪ Everybody's gonna die ♪
♪ Have a dark and dead July! ♪
Fat chicks with black hair
get tattoos of me!
God, I love this time of year.
It's just past
all the amazing colors of fall,
and before the white of winter.
Just brown and gray.
Magical.
All right, let's do this.
All right, listen up,
I'm the captain.
The teams are chosen by
a lottery system where...
Aunt Karen, can I
be on your team?
Yeah, yeah, me, too!
Uh, yeah, sure,
I'll take, uh,
Meg, Skinny,
Hot Chocolate and The Bus.
Pee Pee, you get
the crumbs.
Let's go.
All right, let's do it, Pop!
I'm gonna make some
sports points for you!
We'll kick off.
Hey, time-out!
Did anyone tape the parade?
Please tell me
someone taped the parade!
Oh, my God! She's
doing The Toxic Shock!
Y-Y-You're a j-jerk, K-K-Karen!
What the hell was that?
That's his stutter.
And whenever he stutters,
he usually pees his pants.
N-No, I... d-d-don't.
Oh.
So this is football.
I like it.
Hi, Dad.
Look, I-I just want you to know,
I feel bad about what happened
with you and Aunt Karen
the other day.
Oh, you mean when she put me in
that no-bottom James Bond chair
and assaulted my grundle?
I didn't even
know about that.
Well, that's 'cause
it didn't happen.
I'd kick her ass if she
tried something like that!
Dad, stop. Even I can see
that your sister's a huge bully.
And trust me, I know more about
getting bullied than anyone.
You do? How?
♪ Celebrate good times,
come on ♪
♪ Let's celebrate ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Celebrate good times,
come on. ♪
Man, I love that song.
Dad, what I'm trying
to tell you is,
I now see why you've been
so tough on me all these years.
'Cause it makes
my friends laugh?
No, because that's how
Aunt Karen treated you
when you were a kid.
That's right. And that's why
you need to confront Karen.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
No, I can't do that.
I tried for years
to stand up to her.
Nothing ever worked.
What, so now
you're gonna quit?
You can't quit.
What if Muhammad Ali had quit?
Ah, my grandchildren!
Who would like me
to read them a book,
or maybe paint their name
on a grain of rice?
Honey, dinnertime!
Ah, my favorite.
Hot soup.
Right in there.
Dad, I know you can
stand up to Aunt Karen.
And maybe if you finally do,
she'll stop terrorizing you,
and you won't have to
take it out on me
for the rest of my life.
You know what, Meg?
You're right!
I'm gonna do it!
You are?
Damn right!
Yay, Dad!
I am gonna become
a lady wrestler
and defeat Heavy Flo
in the ring.
Wait. What?! No! What?!
I meant go talk to her.
Nope, it's got to be a
lady wrestling match.
Hey, Meg,
Thanksgiving's over.
Come help me
with the Christmas decorations.
Meg! Help me with
the Christmas decorations!
Comments? Questions?
What the hell are you...
I'm sorry. Chris had
his hand up first.
Chris?
What's the capital
of Maryland?
I do not know, but that's
a very good question.
Now, Lois?
Peter, what the hell
are you doing?!
First, it's not Peter.
When I am in this outfit,
I am Maxi Paddy,
the fiercest enemy of Heavy Flo.
Peter, you look--
okay, that's clever--
but, Peter,
you look ridiculous.
Take that off.
If you want to settle things
with your sister,
just go talk to her.
No, Lois, the only way to
settle a family dispute
is in the cage.
I mean, you don't understand.
Karen made me feel worse than
a guy getting cut
from a baseball team.
You wanted to
see me, Coach?
I'm sorry, Kyle.
You can't do this boring,
stupid thing with us.
All right, Peter,
your sister's the real deal.
So I arranged for you
to get some combat pointers
from my old buddy,
Steven Seagal.
Uh, this... this fat guy?
Yup. Go on, ask him anything.
How... how did...?
Uh, why-why you so fat?
Okay, ask him about
anything but his weight.
Uh...
uh, you act Asian,
you look Native American,
your name is possibly Jewish.
What are you?
He fat.
All right, Peter,
most professional wrestlers
become addicted to painkillers
at some point.
So I figure,
why don't we just start now?
Uh... okay,
yeah, I'm in.
Where you getting
all these?
Stepdaughter's purse.
Ain't my problem.
Man, I love putting my hand down
my pants when I'm on drugs.
We should just go live on a
boat in some guy's backyard.
So, you gonna do
that wrestling stuff?
Nah, I'm gonna
stick with these.
I would crime
for more of these.
Okay, now if you're gonna defeat
your sister in the ring,
you got to get to the root
of your fears.
We got to go back
to your childhood,
so I'm gonna
hypnotize you.
Okay, go back.
Now, we need to go
back in time.
My jeans are husky.
Okay, further. Further.
Little further.
Now, open your eyes
and tell me what you see.
I see the six
stations of the Lord's order,
and they will all burn!
Okay, too far!
Too far! Too far!
Come back. Come back.
Come back.
Hey,
can I make my husky jeans
into cutoffs
for swimming?
Ah, forget it. You're ready.
Yeah, Peter.
I think you're gonna win!
All right! Hey, thanks for
all your help, you guys.
You know, there's
only two things
I've wanted to do
my whole life:
put my sister in her place
and go to Chico's Monkey Farm.
♪ ♪
♪ Chico's Monkey Farm ♪
♪ Come and have
a howling good time ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, aah-aah,
ooh-ooh, aah-aah ♪
♪ Chico's Monkey Farm ♪
♪ The only drive-through
monkey farm ♪
♪ In Northern
Southern Rhode Island ♪
♪ Ooh, aah! ♪
♪ Chico's Monkey Farm ♪
♪ After a prolonged litigation,
we're finally open again ♪
♪ Ooh, aah! ♪
♪ Chico's Monkey Farm ♪
♪ There's a fair amount
of paperwork ♪
♪ Before you get to see a monkey
so allow for extra time ♪
♪ Ooh, aah! ♪
♪ Chico's Monkey Farm ♪
♪ Keep your windows rolled up
'cause the monkeys ♪
♪ Will pry 'em open and
they're known to strangle kids ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh, aah-aah-aah! ♪
Chico's Monkey Farm!
Now open pending how it goes.
And we've got quite a match
tonight between Heavy Flo
and another woman
whose name I've forgotten
but I'm sure is a gross pun.
Right you are, Bill.
Tonight, she's up against
Her Vajesty's Secret Cervix.
Interesting fact:
these two gals have
over eight meters of
ass crack between them.
One! Two! Three!
It's over!
And once again, a Heavy Flo has
ruined another lady's evening!
You ain't no champ!
Not till you go through me!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Maxi Paddy, which is
short for Maxine Patricia.
I was named after my father,
Maxwell Patrick.
But that's enough about me.
I'm here to kick your ass!
Get out of here!
I'm not fighting some fat loser
from the crowd.
Huh. It looks like
this Heavy Flo is pee,
because you're yellow!
Oh!
Well, that didn't
quite track,
but the crowd
seems to be on board.
It sure does!
Looks like Heavy Flo
has a challenger!
All right, get up here,
but make it quick.
I got a Lampoon
reunion to get to.
Heavy Flo, always
finding a way
to drop her Harvard degree
into conversation.
Yes, very
off-putting, Bill.
Those of us who went to Harvard
really don't appreciate it.
Ow! Damn it, Karen!
Karen?
Peter, is that you?
What are you doing here?
Something I should have done
a long time ago.
I'm tired of you bullying me!
You're going down!
Butt-scratcher?!
Butt-scratcher!
♪ ♪
D-D-D-Don't, K-K-Karen!
Toxic Shock! Toxic Shock!
Oh, my God,
she's taking it too far!
Heavy Flo is gonna break
this girl's arms!
Woman's arms.
Come on, Bill.
N-N-No!
Tell... Stewie...
he's in charge of the show now.
Say hello to Teen LaQueefa!
One! Two! Three!
I don't believe it!
Heavy Flo is down, and
we have a new champion!
I tell you, this is
one for the books,
if anyone kept track
of this nonsense!
Wow, you really
saved me!
Thanks, stranger.
Dad, it's me.
Meg?
It was you who saved me?
That's right, Dad.
Wow, even after all the
crummy stuff I've done to you?
But why?
Because you're my dad.
And I couldn't stand by
and watch you get hurt.
Wow. Thanks, Meg.
You know, that's something
even my own mom and dad
never did for me.
They just stood by and
let Karen pick on me.
Well, you deserve better.
We all do.
You know, Meg, I'm really sorry
I treated you so badly
over the years.
I guess I was taking out
all the pain I felt on you.
I understand.
Better than anybody.
But I still love you, Dad.
I love you, too, Meg.
Did somebody order
a hot-ass bitch and this lady?
Oh, you're alive.
Sorry, I was told
I was in charge now.
Well, if you die,
this is kind of
the creative direction
I'm leaning toward.
Well, I'm proud of you, Dad.
You finally stood up
for yourself.
So, Peter,
have you talked to Karen?
I called, like, four times, but
she's not out of the coma yet.
Apparently, they usually
use fake chairs,
but Meg used a real one.
Do they think
she's gonna survive?
It could go either way.
Hello? No, I think I'm a
different blood type.
No, I don't
want to check.
Doctor says there's
nothing they can do.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru